Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - Lake Shore Drive (Map-case Folder 82)
    - Blueprint plans of boulevard: Sheets 1 and 2 (Map-case Folder 83)
  - Eugene Meyer (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Details of Orangerie by Charles A. Platt, architect, August 1916 (Map-case Folder 84)
  - John Magee (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Marble work details (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Memo for brick parapet (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Pergola details (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Pergola and fountain terrace (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Details of marble work in garden (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Planting plan of bulbs, perennials and biennials (Map-case Folder 84)
  - Mr. and Mrs. S. Morris (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Bulb planting plan, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Shrub planting plan, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Perennial planting plan, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Construction plan of garden, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Planting plan of annuals and chrysanthemums, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Revised perennial planting plan, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Drainage plan, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Presentation plan, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Sketch of tea house, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Construction plan of pool, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Construction details of wall fountain, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Detail of garden gate, 1923 (Map-case Folder 84)
  - William G. Mather (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Detail of a garden gate between garden and forecourt, April 27, 1908 (Map-case Folder 84)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Hugh D. Marshall (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Planting plan for flower garden, April 1944 (Map-case Folder 84)
  - Miss Margaret Matney (Map-case Folder 84)
    Location: Brewster, New York
    - Planting plan of garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 84)
    - Suggested development of front entrance, 1945 (Map-case Folder 84)
  - Mrs. Theodore A. McGraw (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Planting plan for shrubs and vines for south-west border of garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Planting plan of court garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Construction details for oak seat, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Planting plan for north and east terraces, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Construction details of front terrace, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - First floor plan of residence, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Annual picking and reserve garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Shrubs and bulb planting plan for main garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Shrub and tree general planting plan, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Construction plan of garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Flower planting plan for main garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
    - Sketch plan for the garden, 1924 (Map-case Folder 85)
  - Mr. and Mrs. George P. MacNichol (Map-case Folder 86)
    - General construction drawing for flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Planting plan for perennials in flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Detail plan for paving for the house terrace and garden walk, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Details for dovecote in flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Construction drawing for northwest terrace, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Planting plan for fall chrysanthemums, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Planting plan for spring bulbs, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Construction drawing for repaving terraces, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Suggested change in entrance court, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Design plan (Black and What), 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Revised design plan (Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Construction drawing for northwest terrace gate, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Alternate design for flower garden, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Construction drawing for flower garden gate, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Planting plan for terraces, 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Suggestion for the terrace and rock garder (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - Topographic plan (Black and White), 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
    - First floor plan of house (Blueprint), 1944 (Map-case Folder 86)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Taylor Mead (Map-case Folder 86)
    Location: Windsor, Vermont
    - General plan, 1943 (Map-case Folder 86)
  - Mrs. Thomas O. Moore (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Design plan (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Map of property (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Design plan - Sketch A (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Design plan - Sketch B (2 Black and White) (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 87)
    - Residence (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 87)
    - General design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 87)
  - Darwin D. Martin (Map-case Folder 87)
    Location: Lakeview, New York
    - Revised design plan 1, 1930 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 214
    - Heavy planting of east boundary, 1931 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 214, Plan 5
    - Revised heavy planting of east boundary, 1931 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 214, Plan 5A
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for house area, 1930 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 199, Plan 3
    - General tree and planting plan for estate, 1930 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 199, Plan 2
    - Plating plan for evergreen garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 214, Plan 4
    - Revised design plan 1, 1929 (Map-case Folder 87)
      File 199
    - Plan for country home on shore of Lake Erie by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1929 (Map-case Folder 87)
  - Mrs. F.S. Moseley (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Layout plan of laundry yard (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Construction details (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 88)
    - General design plan (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Garden gate (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Planting plan for perennial border (Map-case Folder 88)
  - Mr. and Mrs. C.G. Martin (Map-case Folder 88)
    Location: Chattanooga, Tennessee
    - Plan for brick paving in flower garden (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Sketch plan for tea house (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Screen planting plan for west boundary (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Shrub planting plan for children's garden (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Planting plan of perennials, roses, and ground covers (Map-case Folder 88)
    - Planting plan of trees, shrubs, and vines (Map-case Folder 88)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Louis Mendelsonn (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Alternate design plan (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Sketch of wall and pool at fountain (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Landscape design plan (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Preliminary construction plan (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Sketch plan (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Garden and road plan (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Preliminary Plan I (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Preliminary Plan I (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Preliminary Plan II (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Design plan for garden (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Planting plan for entrance terrace (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Construction plan for proposed wall and pool (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Construction plan for pool (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Construction layout plan (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Plan for revision of existing garden (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Planting plan "B" for perennial garden (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Planting plan "A" for perennial garden (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Planting plan "A" for trees and shrubs (Map-case Folder 89)
    - Planting plan "B" for trees and shrubs (Map-case Folder 89)
  - Miss Emma Martin (Map-case Folder 90)
    Location: Princeton, New Jersey (Edgestone)
    - Planting plan for terrace, 1938 (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Planting plan for section E, flower garden, 1938 (Map-case Folder 90)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Kenneth Mountcastle (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Planting plan for area around house (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Planting for staking out driveway (Map-case Folder 90)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Plans of house (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Plan A for locations of buildings (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Plan B for locations of buildings (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Topographic map (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 90)
  - Mr. and Mrs. J.E. Murdock (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Preliminary design plan A (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Planting plan for trees, shrubs, and vines (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Preliminary design B (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Survey (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 90)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 90)
  - Dr. Frederick Murphy (Map-case Folder 91-92)
    - Construction plan for pool (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Details of niche and fountain (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Design for entrance court (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Plans of house (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Details of new brick terrace (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Details in garden (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Details of balustrade (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Revised sketch for terrace (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Revised plan of parking space (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Construction drawing of garden (VOID) (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Revised plan for fountain wall (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Furniture plan for bedroom and sitting room (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Details of iron steps and platform (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Preliminary sketch for garden (WP) (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Design plan for terraces (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Tree, shrub, and vine planting plan of pool terrace (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Tree, shrub, and vine planting plan of central and dining terrace (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan of entrance (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Perennial planting plan of pool terrace (Map-case Folder 91)
    - Perennial planting plan of central and dining terraces (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Bulb planting plan of central and dining terraces (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Shrub border planting plan (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Central construction plan for south terrace (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Details of open balustrade (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Survey of property (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Revised planting plan for shrub border (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Sketch of foundation wall (VOID) (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Sketch of fountain wall (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Dimension plan for driveway (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Details of console and niche (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Design for entrance court (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Plan and details of forecourt (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Proposed plan sketch (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Sketch plan of porch (Map-case Folder 92)
    - layout plan of tree and shrub border (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Sketch plan for flower gardens (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Planting plan for screens near house (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Planting plan for shrub border (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Detail of iron gate (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Sketch of east and west walls (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 92)
  - Mrs. T. McGraw (Map-case Folder 92)
    - Suggestion for layout of flagstone terrace (Map-case Folder 92)
  - George W. Coan Sr., Esq. (Map-case Folder 93)
    - Elevations, basement, first floor, second floor, third floor >lb/>and attic plans for house including some interior elevations (blueprints.), 1935 (Map-case Folder 93)
      William Wallace Architect
  - Mrs. Ormsby Mitchell (Map-case Folder 94-96)
    - Details of wrought iron flower stand (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Details of wooden door at dovecote (Map-case Folder 94)
    - General design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 94)
    - General layout plan (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Photostats of house plans (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Interior perspective (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Planting plan for rose garden (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Shrub planting plan for long borders (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Shrub planting plan for entrance (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Plan for revision of terrace I (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Measured drawing of living room alcove (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Perennial planting plan for pool garden (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Perennial planting plan for entrance (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Perennial planting plan for perennial border (Map-case Folder 94)
    - General construction plan for entrance piers and wall (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Detail of entrance wall (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Details of pier caps (Map-case Folder 94)
    - Detail of garden wall (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Revised road plan (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Proposed road plan (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Plan of living room (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Construction details for steps (Map-case Folder 95)
    - New shrub and perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Shrub planting plan for pool garden (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Revised details of parapet (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Shrub planting plan for terraces 1 and 2 (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Details of parapet (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Construction details of entrance court (Map-case Folder 95)
    - General layout plan for garden (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Construction details for round pool (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Construction details for pool in paved garden (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Hardware for dovecote doors (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Details of wooden door in entrance gate (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Plan showing wall heights (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Plan showing location of house (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Continuation of elevation of east wall (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Elevations of south wall of terrace 1 (Map-case Folder 95)
    - Construction details of entrance gate arch (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Location plan of lighting fixtures and outlets (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Plan of drainage and water supply system (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Construction detail of door dovecote (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Elevation of west wall of terrace 1 (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Plan and elevation of parapet along terrace 2 (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Survey of Shaw property (Photostat) (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Revised plan for area by dovecote (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Plot plan (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Topographical map (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Specifications for pump house (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Alternate design plan (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Revised design plan (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Plan showing location of terraces (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Details of balustrade (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 96)
    - Template and details of door in yard wall (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 96)
  - Mrs. Holden McGinley (Map-case Folder 97-99)
    - Perennial planting plan for perennial garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Shrub planting plan for border below terrace (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Details of service court gate hardware (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Details of front entrance gate hardware (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Details of large service course gate hardware (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Revised shrub planting plan for border below terraces (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Planting plan for upper end of rubble border (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Construction details for wall fountain, rill and pool in Section B (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Existing and proposed road profiles (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Road plan (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Planting plan for two entrance gates (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Presentation plan (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Planting plan for boundary (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Topographic plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Planting plan for area along street (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 97)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Shrub planting plan for path to tennis court (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Revised shrub plan for lower area west of house (Map-case Folder 97)
    - Revised shrub plan for upper area west of house (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Revised shrub plan for peony, iris, and chrysanthemum garden (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Planting plan for rose garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Shrub planting plan for side entrance court (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Perennial planting plan for peony, iris, and chrysanthemum garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Shrub planting plan for perennial garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Planting plan for entrance court (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Plan of entrance gate (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Construction details of round pool in section IV (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Shrub planting plan for outside the garden walls (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Drainage and water supply plan (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Revised shrub planting plan for border below terraces (VOID) (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Planting plan for border below terraces (VOID) (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Elevation of path gate (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Proposed treatment of area west of house (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Construction details for south walls and steps (Map-case Folder 98)
    - General construction plan (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Plans and elevation of service court and driveway gates (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Details of large service court gate (Map-case Folder 98)
    - Detail of small service court gate (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Detail of entrance gate - Sheet 1 (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Detail of entrance gate - Sheet 2 (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Construction details of additional side steps in terrace flight (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Construction details for sections II and IV (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Detail of wall coping in rose garden (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Construction plan for service court (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Sketch of entrance gate (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Construction plan for north wall (2 copies) (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Details of path gate (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Drainage and planting plan of entrance court (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Construction plan of gate posts (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Construction plan of fences (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Road plan (x2) (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Plan for entrance and gates (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Sketches of garden door (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Detail of entrance post (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Plan of residence (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 99)
    - Topographic map of estate (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 99)
  - Albert R. McConnell (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Topographic map of property (4 photostats) (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Preliminary design plan (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 100)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Lynn McNaughton (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Planting plan for standards (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Planting plan for perennials (Map-case Folder 100)
    - General design plan (2 copies, Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 100)
    - General construction plan for wooden fence (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Planting Plan for rose garden (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Design plan for location of lilac walk (Map-case Folder 100)
    - Planting plan for trees (Map-case Folder 100)
    - General construction plan for terrace and garden (Map-case Folder 100)
  - Mrs. Richard Neff (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Design plan for garden, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Construction details - wall fountain and pool, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Construction drawing - garden gate, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Detail of gate post, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Sketches, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Construction drawing for wrought iron rail in flower garden, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Preliminary design plan for gardens - Sketch A (Black and White), 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Preliminary design plan for garden - Sketch B (Black and White), 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Revised construction plan, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Planting plan, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Plan for brick paving (Blueprint), 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Bulb planting plan, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Planting plan, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Detail of base for lead figures, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Planting plan of trees and shrubs for wild walk, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Construction plan showing drainage lines and hose connections, 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
    - Construction plan (Blueprint), 1937 (Map-case Folder 101)
  - Joseph Newall (Map-case Folder 101a)
    Location: New York City, New York
    - Design of garden seat (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 101a)
  - Mr. C.C. Orcutt (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Planting plan for rose garden, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Planting plan for trees and shrubs, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Planting plan for perennial border, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Planting plan around bird bath, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Construction details of bird bath, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - General construction plan, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Preliminary construction drawing, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Plan for path intersection, 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
    - Design plan (Black and White), 1947 (Map-case Folder 101a)
  - Mrs. R. Noble (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Planting plan for spring bloom ground covers (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Planting plan (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Planting plan, section "G" (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Bulb planting plan (Map-case Folder 102)
  - Garden Club (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Sketch plan of garden, undated (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Plot plan for Garden Club (Map-case Folder 102)
  - Unknown (Map-case Folder 102)
    - Miscellaneous Blueprint and Black and White (Map-case Folder 102)
  - Robert Parmelee (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Detail of fence (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Construction details for garden (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Detail of gate in fence (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Bulb and vine planting plan (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 103)
    - General shrub plan (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Shrub plan for garden (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Construction details of seat in garden (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Property survey (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Construction details for garden (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Plan showing fence post spacing (Map-case Folder 103)
    - Construction plan of garden (Map-case Folder 103)
  - James Parmelee (Map-case Folder 104a &B)
    - Planting plan for garden - Sheet B, 1914-05 (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan for garden - Sheets A and B (2 copies of A and 1 of B), 1914-05 (Map-case Folder 104b)
    - Plan of planting of "The Causeway" along brook, 1915-10 (Map-case Folder 104b)
    - Presentation plan of pond, bridle path and grass area, 1915-12 (Map-case Folder 104b)
    - Tree planting plan along bridle path, 1916 (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan for shrubs to border Macomb Street Drive, undated (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Planting plan for additional shrubs to border Macomb Street, 1927 (Map-case Folder 104a)
    - Two sketches for along Macomb Street Drive, 1919 and undated (Map-case Folder 104a)
  - Mrs. James Parmelee (Map-case Folder 104a)
    Location: Painsville, Ohio